

galasmarcin98@gmail.com

in Marcin Galas

C cinek1

#### **SKILLS**

C# Java

**SQL Software Testing** 

HTML, JavaScript, **GIT** 

**CSS** 

**ASP.NET WPF** 

Design patterns

Powershell

#### **LANGUAGES**

# **English**

#### **REFERENCES**

## **Piotr**

Senior Software Developer

"Marcin is promising, solution-oriented engineer with a broad skill set and great ability to learn..."

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Java SE 8 Programmer

Oracle Certified Associate

June 2019

### **HOBBIES**

Football

F1

**Books** 

Modern technologies

Ski

# **Marcin Galas**

Junior Software Enginner

I'm a student of computer science at Jagiellonian University with 1 year comercial experience. I'm inspired by effective work, improving my skills and knowledge, I am a team player, and I enjoy taking on a new challenges and along with my colleagues working through them in order to successfully finilise a project. I have the opportunity to work part time (3/5).

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Dover Fueling Solutions**

Software Engineer Intern

(July 2020 - September 2020)

- Developed embeeded software in .Net core. Created scripts in powershell to pipeline on Team City.
- Worked in scrum team. Everyday used Jirra and Git.

#### Elsta Elektronika Wieliczka

.Net Junior Internship

(September 2019 - June 2020)

- Used Entity framework, nLog and Microsoft SQL server.
- Created documentation to the softwares.

• Developed .Net application in WPF framework.

### **EDUCATION**

#### Jagiellonian University, Krakow

(October 2020 - June 2022)

(October 2017 - July 2020)

Master's degree Computer Science

Faculty of Mathematics and Computer Science

# Jagiellonian University, Krakow

Bachelor's degree Computer Science

Faculty of Mathematics and Computer Science.

#### **PROJECTS**

# Project and implementation of examination system with the use of mobile systems

https://github.com/cinek1/examination-system

I developed backend of the system, Rest api and javascript part to consume this api.

Technologies used:

- C#. ASP. Net core.
- Auth0, Microsoft SQL server, Azure, AutoMapper,
- Javascript, jQuery

# Comparison of face detection libraries available in .Net

https://github.com/cinek1/Comparison-of-face-detection-algorithms-available-in-.Net

The real time application to compare four libraries to face detection avaible in .Net.

Technologies used:

- C#, WPF .Net Core.
- MVVM pattern.
- Autofac to dependency injection.

#### Vet app

https://github.com/cinek1/Vet

Rest Api to for the vet that.

Technologies used:

- Java, Spring, logback
- · postgresSql, JPA
- JUnit, Mockito

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).